It's NOX on Tour Time and today I'm in Bensheim at the StyleFertig headquarters.
They make multifunctional furniture as you can already see in the background
and I'm going to talk with Holger, the CEO and founder. I'm going to show you the
workshop down below, how things are done here, everything in-house and let's go!
It's going to be fun! Alright, with me is Holger, CEO and founder of StyleFertig.
Thanks for having me today. You're welcome. I'm so happy that you can show me not
only your products but also the production i think it's super interesting it is it is welcome in our
facility and uh welcome to the world of kinky furniture you're the world leading manufacturer
for multi-functional furniture right you can have a lot of fun with our with the furniture and yes
we deliver all over the world and uh in my opinion we are the world leader the people know what is
I've seen the Style Fetish products in Bangkok.
Bangkok, yeah.
Yes, Red Studio, Mr. S.
Right, right.
Shout out to Mr. S. Greetings to Thailand.
I know you're all over the world.
Specifically the United States and Europe, Australia.
But it's all produced here in Germany in a really small town, actually quite near to
where I live.
So all produced in-house.
Right.
You do everything yourself.
I do it by myself and my employers.
We have a team of 10 people who are working with us.
And yeah, we are very proud to say
everything is crafted by hand here in Germany, in Bensheim.
We give nothing away.
So everything is under control of Style Fetish Germany.
And it begins with the cutting of the steel bars,
with the welding work, powder coating works.
Everything is powder coated in house here
in the color you want.
We do the upholstery works.
Everything is padded here with my team
our team is doing all this upholstery stuff. We do the assembling here in-house and of course,
the packaging, shipping, engineering, pictures, promotion, marketing.
So everything is made in-house here. So these are the three stages of that piece?
That's correct. That's the first stage. Right. As you can see, that's a plyboard and that's the
basic which all the paddings are made from. So we have a plyboard, a plywood, then we add some
foam material and a fox leather this is really soft that's really soft yeah it's really thick and
this is german saying we are very accurate as you can see all the staples are in line they look so
neat it's not like crisscross this is a sling bed a hanging sling bed we can have a lot of fun with
it's also a baby maker this is the assembly facility of style fetish you can see over there
there's a poly coating on it everything come over here and here's the assembling all the assembling
works if you could choose one product for yourself and only do that oh which one would it be that's
that's a difficult question because um you have different positions you can play you can you have
you can have a session while you're sitting while you're like doggy style so we can specifically for
doggy style I can recommend or my personal favorite is a Hellcat chair the
Hellcat bench. So the Hellcat is one of your bestsellers? I would say a Hellcat is one
of the most favorite item. Wow okay yeah and why is it so special? Because it's
flexible you can you can use it for every position you can imagine and you
can extend it with more attachments you can even you can use it as a bench.
I'm gonna beep that one.
Okay, you can even use it as a bench for activities, you know what I mean?
On your knees and your elbows.
But you can also attach, for example, a gyno table on top.
And then you can sit reverse, like on a relaxed chair.
So what's this?
All right, this one is called the Pussy or Butt Box, as you can imagine.
We have to beep that one.
The name says it all.
The person who was laying inside will be reduced to...
So there will be a top here to close it.
It's closed.
You can open and close it.
I can show you.
Yeah, we can see the finished one.
This is the opening for the feet and the back of your body.
The nicest part of the body.
Nicest part will be in this position.
It looks very comfortable.
know it looks like a magician's box right right yeah it's a magician box right and it's completely
padded inside we have the air track system to use airline belts and um you can imagine how it feels
yeah right yeah so to get inside makes it much easier we have hatches over here on both sides
for padding. I love that there is everywhere padding and it's really thick. Right, right. It's
thick and it looks cozy and it's cozy and comfortable of course. There's a lot of work
as you can imagine and plywood is made on a point by point machine, point to point machine and
And yeah, we love details.
And I love that everything is like...
It's on wheels, right?
On wheels?
It's hot wheels.
I always think this looks like a Pokemon,
like a Snorlax.
It's just playing around.
And it's pretty comfy.
And pretty multifunctional.
I've seen these parts here on a lot of furniture.
and you can attach or detach stuff here, as you can see.
And it's a pretty handy system.
You actually only need one hand to quickly detach it,
and then you can attach it elsewhere.
If I would be tall enough,
I could attach it to the ceiling, for example.
As you can see, we have already some hanging here,
or I can attach it to a different piece of furniture.
And it fits everywhere, so it's a one-fits-all system.
So how did you start a company? Did you wake up one day and said I want to do Kinky Furniture for a living?
Right, exactly that way. No, so I was in a relationship with a girl and she was working as a
dominatrix, it's 25 years ago and one evening she took me with her in the dark room and there was an
old creepy shitty slave chair and i said oh my gosh never mind i would never sit naked on that
on the chair i built a better one for you so that's what you did you built your better chair
the right that was the starting of course wow and then you grew a lot you said 10 employees right
how long do you do you start 30 is that something like 20 years 25 years we had a 25th anniversary
last year. We have a lot of companies who are working with us delivering like
steel rods, steel bars. Normally we need more employees but Ten is perfect for me.
So my nerves and that's perfect for me. So if somebody wants to order something
you have a web shop? Yeah of course we have an online shop it's stylefittish.de
Of course there's another one from North America it's running by a partner
bike partner in the US. It's StyleFitness-Industries.com.
Okay, I'll link everything in the description text.
Perfect.
So everyone can click on that.
You can order everything online. You can even go in touch with us by phone, by email.
Can people visit here in the showroom?
Of course. People can come over, just make a little appointment.
Yeah. And customers can customize their furnitures. So I've seen you've done some white downstairs.
Right.
And I see a lot of black, but I also see something green, metallic.
Right, so we have a basic program which is called the flagship series.
The most wanted items we have on the production line and those products are for the mainstream.
But not only for the mainstream.
Imagine you have special wishes, special desires.
We can even customize also flagships product.
If you run a studio or you run a club, it might be possible that you need any customizations
like colors, upholstery, special dimensions. We will customize. If you really want, we can do that.
All right. So I'm going to order my pretty pink chair. No problem. No problem. We'll do that.
Thanks again for answering these questions and having me. Thank you. I had a lovely time here
today at Style Fetish. I hope you enjoyed it too. If you want to learn more about the products,
check out the homepage of Style Fetish. I'll link everything down in the description text,
of course and let me know what your favorite part was and I hope you enjoyed it.
I will see you in the next video. Have a nice day. Bye.